<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>oh, there you are</title>
    <description>oh, there you are - a live culture travel production by the philotic connection.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 07:13:41 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 07:13:41 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Orleans Top 5</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;Top 5 Restaurants in New Orleans&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;our take on the best of #nolaeats after a first whirlwind trip.&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's painful to try to put them in any kind of order. It's tough to get a bad meal in the big easy, but for us, Peche, Cane and Table, Atchafalaya, Shaya, and Bacchanal rose to the top of the foodie chain. Here's the run-down:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Peche&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peche Seafood Grill is a Spanish, Gulf Coast, South American inspired seafood restaurant at the edge of the CBD (Central Business District). The food was amazing and the staff was great. We had reservations for a Monday night dinner at 7pm and it was packed so we recommend making reservations ahead of time. When you get there make sure to start off with a drink and their Seafood Salad which is kind of their take on ceviche. Don’t leave without trying the Roasted Carrots, Fried Bread, Spicy Ground Shrimp and Noodles, and Crawfish Capellini.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/peche.friedBread.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;It says something when the food is so good you forget to take any pictures at all. The fried bread was simply wonderful. Photo courtesy of @pechenola&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;!-- &lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;video width=&quot;100%&quot; controls autoplay muted loop&gt;
    &lt;source src=&quot;/assets/images/mardigras.octopus.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
 --&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Cane and Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arguably tied with first place in our hearts, but Cane and Table really is a hidden gem in New Orleans. I hope it stays that way because the service, food, and drinks were on a whole other level - even compared to other cities we’ve visited. Cane and Table would be the best place to go to in any city, New Orleans is lucky to have it. We were walking through the french quarter on our way to Cafe Du Monde on the first morning, stumbled across this place and drank our way through their entire brunch cocktail menu instead #priorities ($35 all you can drink with an entree special! AMAZING!!!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/caneandtable.cocktails.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Whoa. I guess it's gone already.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  We were walking through the french quarter on our way to Cafe Du Monde on the first morning, stumbled across Cane and Table and drank our way through their entire brunch cocktail menu instead.
  &lt;cite&gt;#priorities&lt;/cite&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Atchafalaya&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Atchafalaya is nestled in right at the border of the Garden District and Uptown - sitting on a beautiful wide avenue. They had a build your own Bloody Mary bar, alligator sausage (a bit tangy, but yeah, tastes a bit like a mix of chicken and fish), the best Pimms Cup we found on had the whole trip, and the best Chicken and Biscuits we’ve tried anywhere! Go and tell me I’m wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/alligator.sausage.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Atchafalaya's alligator sausage - a bit tangy, but yeah, tastes a bit like a mix of chicken and fish.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Shaya&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shaya is an Israeli inspired restaurant located in Uptown, lives up to its reputation as one of the best restaurants in the country. The decor, the service, the pita bread!!! All of it was amazing. You want to make sure to come hungry, we tried almost everything and left regretting nothing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/shaya.lamb.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;We thought we were going to be too full by the time the lamb came out. But, you guessed it. We powered through.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Bacchanal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We almost regret having to share this gem with the internet but Bacchanal Wine is not ours to keep secret. #moraldilemma. This place is the epitome of perfection to us. It reminds of every amazing night out in every great city we’ve been to with its outside patio and live music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/bacchanal.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Bacchanal in the Bywater&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe it was because it was our last night in New Orleans or the perfect weather or the amazing music or the Lambrusco or the Cheese or the Bread or because I guess we’re kind of suckers for a great charcuterie board but something about it left us feeling home sick for New Orleans and we hadn’t even left yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Let's be honest. It's hard to find a bad meal in nola&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not that we plan to try, but this is a freaking-awesome list amongst thousands of freaking-awesome options. Keep eating, nola eaters. Try it all, but if you’re looking for the best - we say you give these spots a shot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until next time, nola.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/02/25/nola-top-5/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/02/25/nola-top-5/</guid>
        
        
        <category>destination nola</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
